Oh! Hey, Rach.
저런, 레이첼
내가 여기 왜 왔냐면...
I was just coming over here to...
Wait, I don't have to lie to you,
you don't live here anymore.
참, 거짓말할 필요 없지?
너 이제 여기 안 사는데
뭐 좀 먹을까 하고
넌 여기서 뭐해?
I'm eating their food.
You?
로스가 내 동생이랑
데이트 중인데
Ross is on a date with my sister.
They shut the drapes two hours ago.
두 시간 반 전부터
커튼까지 내리고 있어
네 동생이랑
만나도 되는 거였어?
I didn't know we could
date your sister.
조이, 훔쳐먹는 거 다 알아
We know you steal our food.
난 됐다
I'm good.
Drapes still closed?
커튼은 아직 그대로야?
그래, 커튼은 옆집의 늙은이
변태 커플이 쳐야 하는데
Yeah. That perverted couple
two doors over should've shut theirs.
- 저거 부부교환 아냐?
- 대답하기도 싫어
-Is that a swing?
-Oh, don't even ask.
I can't believe Ross
is with her sister.
로스가 레이첼 동생이랑
데이트를 하다니
챈들러가 내 동생 만났을 때
난 10년이나 화를 냈었는데
When Chandler kissed my sister,
I was mad for 10 years.
-That was five years ago.
-You got five years left.
5년 전 일이야
그니까 5년 더 남았어
-Joey..
-Want to make it six?
- 조이...
- 6년으로 해주랴?
The One Where Chandler Can't Cry
Oh, Ross, hey. Hi, how are you?
There you are.
로스, 여기 있었네?
그래
커피요
Can I get a cup of coffee?
So how was your big date last night?
어젯밤 데이트는 어땠어?
뭐 괜찮았어
재미도 있었고
It was okay. It was fun.
- 재미있었어?
- 그래
It was fun?
Great.
잘됐네
그래서 둘이 잘 맞는 것 같아?
So did you guys hit it off?
I guess so.
그런 대로
별일은 없었니? 커튼까지
내렸다는 소문이 들리던데
So did anything happen?
Rumor has it you guys shut the drapes.
No. No. Nothing happened.
아냐, 아무 일도 없었어
커튼은 화석 슬라이드
보여주려고 내린 거야
I shut the drapes to show her
slides of my favorite fossils.
Oh, slides!
슬라이드라...
진짜 아무 일도 없었구나
So really nothing happened.
Something could've happened.
꼭 그렇지만도 않아
내 슬라이드를
엄청 좋아하더라고
She really dug my slides.
And she was definitely
giving me the vibe.
게다가 분명 나한테
야시시한 눈길을 줬어
세상에
Was it the "Please don't show me
another picture of a trilobite" vibe?
그건 삼엽충 사진 좀 그만
보여 달라는 눈길 아니었을까?
I'm telling you,
she was in to me, okay?
분명 날 좋아하고 있어
저런
Hey, you remembered trilobite.
삼엽충을 아직 기억하네?
어쨌든...
Anyway...
내가 맘에 안 들었다면
왜 또 만나자고 했겠니
If she wasn't into me,
why would she ask me out again?
- 또 만나자고 했어?
- 아무렴
-She asked you out again?
-Yeah.
Tomorrow night. Valentine's Day.
The most romantic day of the year.
내일 밤
1년 중 가장 낭만적인
발렌타인데이에
무슨 일 생길지 누가 알아?
Who knows what could happen.
I might not be shutting my drapes
to show her my slides.
슬라이드 말고 다른 이유로
커튼을 내릴지도 모르지
그래, 알아들었어
거기까지만 해
Okay! I got it, I got it.
동생 얘기는 그만
더는 못 듣겠어
I can't go with the "you
and my sister" thing.
It's just too weird, all right?
너무 끔찍해
둘이 함께 있는 거
생각만 해도 소름 끼쳐
I imagine the two of you together.
It just freaks me out.
I can't do it!
- 도저히 참을 수 없어
- 그래, 알았어, 그만해...
알았다니까
It's okay.
그래, 네 생각이 그렇다면
다신 안 만날게
It's too weird for you.
I won't see her again.
고마워
Thank you.
내일 하루만 보고
After tomorrow night.
안 돼, 그러지 마
나 미칠 것 같아
No! I can't do it.
It's gonna freak me out!
그래, 알았어
Okay, okay, okay!
좋아, 오늘 얘기할게
이제 만나지 말자고
Okay. I'll tell her tonight
I can't see her anymore.
정말 고마워
Ross, thanks.
지금 당장 전화할까?
Want me to call her now?
아냐, 아니지...
Oh, no. No, no, no.
말도 안 돼
그건 진짜 심하다
No. Come on, I mean, that's crazy.
넌 요새 어떻게 지내니?
So, what's going on with you?
그게...
Well...
참! 이번 학기에
다른 강의를 맡을지도 몰라
I may teach another class
this semester.
그래, 지금 당장 전화해
Do it now. Call her now.
-This is my favorite part.
-Me too.
저 부분이 제일 좋아
나도
뭐가 그렇게 슬퍼?
다 잘 해결됐잖아
I don't know what you guys
are so sad about. It all works out.
E.T. stays with Elliott, and they get to
be best friends forever.
ET랑 엘리엇은 함께 살면서
평생 우정을 쌓을 거고
너 이 영화 봤잖아
ET는 고향으로 돌아가
You've seen this movie before,
E.T. goes back home.
What?
뭐?
Oh, no, I forgot.
젠장, 깜빡했네
You know what's sadder
than this? Bambi.
이거보다 더 슬픈 영화가
뭔 줄 알아? '밤비'야
그거 보고 사흘이나 울었어
I cried for three days
with that movie. No, two.
아니, 이틀이다
The third day my mom killed herself,
so I was partly crying for that.
사흘째는 엄마가 자살하셔서
그것 때문에 운 것 같아
저게 슬픈 건 이해되지만
'밤비'는 만화잖아
Well, that I can see crying
over, but Bambi is a cartoon.
넌 밤비 엄마가 죽을 때도
안 울었냐?
You didn't cry
when Bambi's mother died?
밤비 엄마 그리던 사람은
밥줄 떨어져서 슬펐겠지
Yes, it was very sad when the guy
stopped drawing the deer.
분위기 너무 쳐지니까
채널 돌리자
If this movie's making you guys cry
so much, let's just change the channel.
- 그래
- 좋지?
어때?
There.
Joey, you're crying
over a Doritos commercial.
저건 과자 광고야
I was up for that part.
저 장면 너무 좋아
챈들러, 우는 게 무슨 흉이니?
늘 사내다울 필요는 없잖아
It's okay to cry. You don't
have to be macho all the time.
내가 뭐가 사내답냐?
I'm not macho.
그래, 맞다
Yeah, you're right.
내가 무슨 생각을 한 거지?
I don't know what I was thinking.
난 울어본 기억이
별로 없는 것 같아
I just never really cried.
I'm not a crying kind of guy.
그래도 가슴을 찡하게
만드는 일은 있을 거야
Come on, there's gotta be something
that gets you choked up. Like...
예를 들어...
다리가 셋밖에 없는
강아지를 본다면?
What if you saw a three-legged puppy?
물론 슬프겠지만
I'd be sad, sure.
울진 않을 거야
But I wouldn't cry.
그 강아지가 이래도?
'챈들러, 도와줘요'
What if the puppy said,
"Help me, Chandler.
'다른 강아지들이 날 괴롭혀요'
All the other puppies pick on me."
울어?
Cry? I just found a talking puppy.
I'm rich!
말하는 강아지를 찾으면
벼락부자 되는 거지
I've got it. I have got it.
좋아, 그럼 이건 어때?
Pictures from your childhood.
어릴 때 사진을 보면
기분이 달라질 거야
This'll get you going good.
Oh, what's going on there?
그건 무슨 사진이야?
1학년 때 어버이날인데
Parents' Day. First grade.
내 옆에 계신 분은
수위 마틴 아저씨야
That's me with the janitor, Martin.
-Where are your parents?
-They didn't want to come.
- 부모님은?
- 안 오신다더라고
- 챈들러
- 가엾어라
-Chandler!
-Poor thing.
That story doesn't make you cry?
그래도 안 우니?
No. Look, I don't cry.
It's not a big deal, okay?
아니, 울긴 왜 울어
별일도 아닌데, 안 그래?
아니, 그렇지 않아
No! It's not okay!
It's not okay at all!
한 개도 안 그래
You're dead inside!
넌 정서가 메마른 놈이야
-Excuse me?
-Yeah?
실례합니다
- 네
- 혹시 피비 부페이 양?
-Are you Phoebe Buffay?
-Yeah.
그런데요?
Can I get your autograph?
I'm your biggest fan.
사인 좀 부탁합니다
열렬한 팬이거든요
My biggest fan?
I've always wanted to meet you.
제 열렬한 팬이라고요?
늘 만나보고 싶었어요
Sure. Yeah.
물론 해드려야죠
Wow. Wow, thanks a lot.
정말 감사합니다
I just want to say,
I think you're really talented.
이 말을 꼭 하고 싶었는데
재능이 대단한 분이세요
You're just saying that
because you're my biggest fan.
제 팬이라서
그런 말씀하시는 거죠?
Take good care of that guy.
He's a fan.
조이, 저 사람 접대 잘해
팬이래
Bye.
또 봐요
So you saw me
on Days of Our Lives, huh?
그러니까...
'생의 나날들'에서
절 보셨군요
You want me to do a little
Dr. Drake Ramoray for you?
드레이크 라모레 박사의
대사를 좀 들려드릴까요?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
무슨 말인지 모르겠네요
방금 피비 부페이의
사인을 받았답니다
But I just got Phoebe Buffay's
autograph.
피비의 팬이시군요
Oh. You're Phoebe's fan.
Oh, yeah. I've seen all her movies.
네, 저 여자 영화는 다 봤어요
-Movies?
-That was Phoebe Buffay, the porn star.
영화라뇨?
피비 부페이잖아요
포르노 스타
저런...
I don't think so.
아닌 것 같은데
아뇨, 맞아요
'섹스 토이 스토리 2'에 출연했죠
No, it was. She was in
Sex Toy Story Two...
Lawrence of a Labia.
'아랍여자의 로렌스'에도
사인을 받았답니다
And I got her autograph.
The guys at the comic book store
won't believe this.
만화방 애들이 들으면
기절초풍하겠네
Gunther?
건터
Don't let that guy in here anymore.
He said Phoebe's a porn star.
앞으로 저 친구 받지 말아요
피비더러 포르노 스타래요
Well, I wouldn't call her a star,
but she's really good.
글쎄, 스타까진 아니더라도
상당히 괜찮은 것 같던데
'색골 가제트'를 한번 봐
You should check out
Inspect Her Gadget.
- 언니
- 왔니?
-Hey.
Ross just totally blew me off,
and he didn't even tell me why.
이래도 되는 거야?
로스 오빠가 그만 만나재
특별한 이유도 없이
Oh, well.
저런...
The best thing to do to get over a guy
is to start dating someone else.
남자를 잊는 최선의 방법은
다른 남자를 만나는 거야
Oh! There is this great guy you
will just love at work, named Bob.
참! 우리 회사에 네 맘에
쏙 들 만한 사람이 있다
He's a real up-and-comer
in Human Resources.
인사과의 밥이라고
전도가 참 유망하지
내가 말이 너무 많나?
Maybe I talk too much, or maybe I
should have been more aggressive sexually.
적극적인 섹스어필은 어때?
아니지...
No, no, no.
아냐, 그런 건
로스한테 안 통해
No, that would never
have worked on Ross.
하지만 통하는 상대가 있지
바로 인사과의 밥이야
But you know who that might work on?
Bob in Human Resources.
고맙지만 언니 직장 사람
아무나 만나기는 싫어
Thanks, but I'm not gonna date
some random guy from your work.
아무나라니, 밥이래도
Not random. Bob.
내가 너무 어려 보이나?
모자라 보이든지
It's probably because I'm not
mature enough or smart enough...
옷 입는 게 맘에 안 들었나?
Maybe he doesn't
like the way I dress.
그건 절대 아냐
No, that can't be it.
It's gotta be the smart thing.
모자라 보이는 거야
이런 멍청이, 난 얼굴만
무지하게 예쁜 바보야
I'm so stupid. I'm just this, like,
incredibly pretty, stupid girl.
그게 아냐
No, honey.
좋아, 너 로스가 왜
데이트 취소한 줄 알아?
Okay.
Okay. You want to know why Ross
canceled the date?
내가 그래달라고 부탁했거든
Because I asked him to.
- 언니가 시켰어?
- 그래
You asked him to?
왜?
-Why?
-Because you are my sister...
왜냐면 넌 내 동생이고
로스랑 난 사연이 너무 많아
and Ross and I have
this huge history.
이해가 안 돼
언니 오빠랑 사귈 거야?
-You want to go out with Ross?
-No.
아니
그럼 자기 갖긴 싫고
남 주긴 아까운 거야?
You don't want him,
but you don't want me to have him?
인사과의 밥이란 사람 말이지...
You know, Bob in Human Resources...
기가 막혀서 말이 안 나오네
내 머리까지 의심하게 만들고
I can't believe you did this!
You had me doubting how smart I was!
내 패션감각까지 의심하게 했어
You had me doubting my fashion sense!
별일도 아니잖아, 로스가 뭐야
세상에 널린 게 남자들인데...
It's not that big a deal. Just
don't date Ross. There's other..
나한테 이래라저래라 하지 마
You have no right
to tell me what to do.
이래라저래라가 아니라
이러지 말라는 거야
I'm not telling you what to do.
I am telling you what not to do!
왜 그렇게 날 질투하지?
Why are you so jealous of me?
질투 같은 소리하지 마라
내 꼴이 우스워서 그런다
This is not about me being jealous.
It's about you being a brat,
wanting what you can't have.
먹을 수 없는 걸 탐내잖아
먹을 수 없어?
Can't have?
미안하지만 내가 못 먹는 건
유제품 뿐이야
Excuse me. The only thing
I can't have is dairy!
좋아, 넌 밥과 데이트할
기회를 날린 거야
Well, you just blew your chances
at dating Bob!
- 누구?
- 인사과의 밥!
-Who?
-With Human Resources!
내가 걔를 질투해?
지가 무슨 캐롤라인 공주야?
Jealous of her? Who does she think
she is, Princess Caroline?
캐롤라인 공주는 질투하니?
-You're jealous of Princess Caroline?
-Do I have my own castle?
난 궁전이 없잖아
- 얘들아, 피비 여기 없지?
- 그래
Hey.
-Phoebe's not here, is she?
-No.
비디오 빌려왔어?
Did you get a movie?
맞아, 그렇긴 한데...
Yeah. Yeah.
But I don't think it's the kind
you're gonna like.
너희 맘엔 별로 안 들 거야
밤새도록 휴지를 움켜쥐고
봐야되는 영화는 아니겠지?
Not more movies that'll have us
reaching for the tissues all night?
그럴 수도 있지
Sort of.
무슨 일인데 그래?
What's going on?
피비가 포르노 배우였어
Phoebe's a porn star!
-What?
-Yeah!
- 뭐라고?
- 이게 무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
'피비 부페이 주연
흡혈귀 부인 뒤틀렸네'
"Phoebe Buffay in
Buffay The Vampire Layer."
That's Phoebe.
Where did you get that?
- 세상에
- 피비 맞네, 어디서 빌렸어?
블리커 가의 비디오 대여점
At the adult video place on Bleecker.
조이가 거기 들어가는 걸 보고
And I saw Joey was about to go in,
so I ran in ahead of him...
내가 앞질러 들어갔어
녀석을 놀래줄 작정으로
to surprise him.
그리고는...
이 녀석이 들어오는 걸
못 본 척했거든
Then I pretended that I didn't
know he was in there.
정말 믿을 수가 없다
Wow. I mean,
I just can't believe this.
한 길 사람 속은 모른다더니
I mean, you think you know someone.
아무리 피비가
베일에 싸인 애라지만
Even Phoebe, who's always been
somewhat of a question mark.
진짜 충격이다
This is so bizarre.
불우했던 어린 시절을 생각하면
이해 못할 것도 아니지만
I guess it makes sense.
She had such a terrible childhood.
내 어린 시절도 불우했지만
포르노는 안 찍었어
I had a bad childhood
and I don't do porn.
하지만 넌 정서가 메말랐잖아
Yes, but you're dead inside.
I'd better take that back.
- 그래, 이거 돌려주고 올게
- 잠깐, 왜?
What, why? Why?
그걸 어떻게 봐, 피비라고
We can't watch it.
It's Phoebe.
그래, 맞아
보면 안 되지
We shouldn't watch this.
안 되고말고
반납하고 와
Absolutely not. That goes back.
- 조금만 보면 안 될까?
- 도입부 정도야 뭐
-Maybe a bit.
-The first half?
안 돼, 이러지 마
피비는 우리 친구야
This is wrong, you guys!
Phoebe's our friend!
난 절대 안 볼래
-I'm not gonna watch it.
-Yeah!
그래!
장하다, 조이
Good for you, Joe.
여기 있을 줄 알았어요
노스페라투
I thought I'd find you here,
Nosferatool.
부페이, 그 말뚝을 내 몸에
찔러 넣을 건가요?
Are you going to plunge
your stake into my dark places?
실은 그 반대의 경우를
생각하고 왔거든요
Actually, I was kind of hoping it
would be the other way around.
잠깐, 피비 발목에 뭐야?
What's that on her ankle?
지금 발목이 눈에 들어와?
Her ankle is what you're watching?
잘 안 보이네
Well, it's hard to tell.
그만 좀 움직여라
God, if she would just stop moving.
할 일을 하고 있잖아
She's just doing her job.
변태자식들
You sick bastards!
저건 문신이야
It's a tattoo.
이상한데, 피비는...
That's weird. Phoebe doesn't..
잠깐, 우르술라잖아
Wait, that's Ursula!
That's not Phoebe! That is Ursula!
피비가 아니라 우르술라야
잠깐, 나도 한번 보자
당장 도로 감아
Wait, wait! I can watch that!
Rewind it! Rewind it!
얘들아
Hey.
뭐하는 거야?
What's up? Oh, my God!
What am I doing?!
엄마야, 나 저기서 뭐해!
영혼을 위한 닭고기수프
Hey, sweetie.
- 나 왔어
- 그래
영혼을 위한 닭고기수프?
"Chicken Soup for the Soul"?
이 놈의 소파엔 등받이도 없나?
There's no back to this couch.
왜 이 책을 읽어?
이런 거 싫어하잖아
You hate this kind of stuff.
그래도 한번 읽어보려고
I figured I'd give it a shot.
혹시 눈물나는 얘기가 있으면
메마른 정서가 살아날 거야
One of the stories may make me cry,
then you won't think I'm dead inside.
세상에
Oh, that's so sweet.
눈물 같은 거 안 흘려도
난 자기를 사랑해
I don't care if you can't cry.
I love you.
빈 양철깡통 같은 내 맘을
따뜻하게 감싸주는 말이네
Oh, that makes me feel so warm
in my hollow tin chest.
그만해
Stop it.
아냐, 난 결혼식 올릴 때도
주례 앞에서 이러고 있을 거야
Seriously. We get married, I'm up
at the altar and I'm like this:
난 상관없어
I won't care.
자기 진심은
여기 있을 테니까
I know that you'll be feeling it
all in here.
- 그래?
- 그럼
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
언젠가 우리한테도
아이가 생기고
And if we have a baby one day...
의사가 분만실에서
아기를 안겨줄 때
and the doctor hands it to you
in the delivery room...
네가 울지 않더라도
그게 대수야?
and you don't cry, so what?
또 그 아이를 대학에 보내고
집에 돌아와선
If we take him to college
and come home...
처음으로 아이의 빈방을 볼 때
and we see his empty room
for the first time...
아무 것도 못 느낀다?
and you got nothing?
난 상관없어
It won't matter to me.
좋아
Okay.
그럼 걱정할 필요가 없네?
I won't worry
about this anymore then.
그리고 내가 죽는다?
And then, you know, if I die...
고약한 지병으로 말이지
from a long illness...
조사를 준비하려고
and you're writing my eulogy...
책상 서랍을 열었더니
내 쪽지가 있는 거야
and you open the desk drawer
and find a note from me that says:
'영원히 당신 곁에 있겠어요'
"I will always be with you"...
그때도 자긴 눈물 한 방울
안 흘리겠지만
and you still can't shed
one tiny tear?
마음속으론 눈물이
강물처럼 흐를 거야
I know you'll be
crying a river inside.
-I love you.
-What is wrong with you?!
- 자기를 정말 사랑...
- 너 진짜 이상한 애 아냐!
뭐가?
-What?
죽은 아내를 위해
눈물 한 방울 못 흘려?
You can't shed a tear
for your dead wife?
죽어가면서 글까지 남겼는데?
I left you a note from the beyond!
-So you didn't mean any of that?
-No, you robot!
진심이 아니었어?
아니다, 이 벽창호야!
이 자식들, 또 벨 누르고
달아나면 아주 요절을...
You damn kids! You ring my bell
one more time and I swear..
질
...
Oh, Jill!
저쪽 집 애들이랑 노는 중이야
That's a game I play
with the kids down the hall.
날 너무 좋아하더라고
They've really taken a liking to me.
근데 무슨 일이야?
What's the matter?
언니랑 대판 싸웠어
좀 들어가도 돼?
Rachel and I had a big fight.
Can I come in?
우리 더 이상 만나면
안 되는 건 잘 알지만
I know we're not supposed
to see each other anymore.
지금 내 얘기를 들어줄
사람은 오빠밖에 없어
I don't know anybody in this city
and I need somebody to talk to.
그래, 어떻게 된 건데?
Sure. What happened?
얘기하기도 싫어
I don't want to talk about it.
좋아...
Okay.
지금 위로가 되는 게
뭔지 알아?
-You know what might cheer me up?
-What?
뭔데?
오빠의 그 멋진 슬라이드
Seeing some more of your
super cool slides.
진심이야?
-Wow, really?
-Totally. I loved them.
그럼, 너무 좋아
가지각색의 모래 얘기도
마저 듣고 싶어
You could finish telling me about
the different kinds of sand.
안 될 거 없지, 잠깐 기다려
영사기랑 노트 가져올게
I'd love to. Wait right here, I'll go
get the projector and my notes.
그래, 정말 고마워
오빤 참 좋은 사람이야
Thanks. You're such a good friend.
너희들 혹시 질 못 봤니?
얘가 아무 데도 없어
Have you guys seen Jill?
I can't find her.
난 못 봤는데
-No.
-Is Ross home?
로스는 집에 있나? 전화해서
걔 봤는지 물어봐야겠다
Maybe I'll call him and see
if he's seen her..
누구세요?
Who is it?
It's Phoebe...
나 피비야
피비라고
"Phoebe"!
너 왔니?
-Hey!
-Oh, God!
맙소사
언니 포르노 영화 찍는다면서?
So you're making porn movies.
아닌데
No, I'm not.
카메라 돌아갑니다
We're still rolling!
지금도 찍고 있잖아
You're making one right now!
빨리 갑시다, 피비
Let's go, Phoebe.
게다가 내 이름까지 도용했어
And you're using my name.
내가 뭐 도울 일 있니?
Can I help you with something?
피비, 어서요
Phoebe, come on!
지금 얘기 중이잖아요
아, 언니 부르는구나
Look, I'm talking right now.
You mean her. Oh.
너니까 말인데 쌍둥이를
쓰면 대박이 터진다더라
You know, twin stuff is always
a real big seller.
뭐?
What?
내가 말만 잘하면 너도
지금 30달러 벌 수 있어
I could talk them into giving you...
thirty dollars.
안 돼, 어림도 없어
No! No way! No!
내 이름도 쓰지 마
부끄러운 줄 알아라
And stop using my name!
And shame on you!
당신들도 마찬가지야
하나같이 구역질나
And shame on all of you!
You're disgusting!
특히 덜렁거리는 당신
Especially you, with that!
슬라이드 발진 준비완료
The slides are almost ready.
그래
Yeah.
뭐가 하나 빠졌어
I know what this is missing:
알코올
Alcohol.
주방에 와인이 있을 거야
There's wine in the kitchen.
잘됐다
Oh, great.
여보세요?
내 동생 거기서 뭐 하는데
또 커튼까지 내려놓으셨나?
What is my sister doing there,
and why are the drapes shut?
레이첼, 진정해
Okay. Rach, calm down, okay?
지금 감정이 격한 상태라
내가 달래는 중이야
She's really upset.
We're just talking.
걔 지금 나 뒤통수치려고
너랑 일 저지르려는 거야
She's making something happen
with you to get back at me.
단지 그것 때문에
여기 왔다고 생각해?
That's the only reason
she could be here, huh?
혹시라도 내가 남의
얘기를 잘 들어주고
It couldn't be that maybe
I'm a good listener...
기막힌 슬라이드 쇼까지
준비한 건 모르겠지?
and I put on a great slide show?
로스, 다시 말하지만 걘 지금
나 때문에 널 이용하는 거야
Ross, I am telling you,
she is using you to get back at me.
내 일은 내가 알아서 해
다음에 얘기하자, 그럼
I think I can take care of myself.
I'll talk to you later. Goodbye.
언니 전화였어
That was your sister, actually.
네가 날 이용한다고
생각하던데?
She thinks you're just using me.
So?
그래서?
- 나야
- 어서 와
-Hey.
방금 우르술라 언니가
일하는 회사에 다녀왔어
I just came from the company
Ursula works for.
Oh, no, not you too?
안 돼, 너마저?
아니, 내 몫의 수표를 챙기러
갔던 것 뿐이야, 엄청 많더라
I went to get Phoebe Buffay's checks.
There were a lot of them.
잘했다
Nice!
게다가 이젠
또 갈 필요도 없어
And I won't have to
go back there anymore...
내 정확한 주소를
알려주고 왔거든
because I gave them
my "correct address."
그건 좋은데
Isn't it gonna bother you
that people think you're a porn star?
사람들이 널 포르노 배우로
생각해도 괜찮겠어?
그럼, 다 준비해둔 게 있어
Oh, no, I know how to handle it.
- 정말?
- 그래
-Good.
-Yeah.
날 어디서 봤는지
기억이 안 나죠?
Trying to figure out how you know me?
힌트 하나 줄게요
포르노예요, 됐죠?
I'll give you a hint. From porn!
당신의 변태 남자친구가
날 포르노에서 봤대요
Yeah, your pervert boyfriend
watched me in a porno movie!
-See?
-Yeah.
- 봤지?
- 그래
왔냐?
Hey.
네 얘기가 맞았나 봐
You may have been right about Jill.
그럴 줄 알았어
어떻게 됐는데?
I knew it! What happened?
나한테 키스를 하더라
She kissed me.
뭐? 키스를 했어?
What? You kissed?
자릴 비켜줘야겠는데?
Maybe we should
give them some privacy...
들어봐, 난...
안 하려고 노력했어
Look, I tried not to kiss her, okay?
글쎄, 누구랑 키스를 안 하는 데
노력씩이나 필요한 거야?
Doesn't sound like it.
It's easy not to kiss someone.
You just don't. Look at us
right now, not kissing!
우릴 봐, 지금 키스하니?
내 말 끝까지 들어
질이 키스하는데...
Let me finish, okay?
She started kissing me...
난 멈추지 못했어
정신이 없었으니까
and I didn't stop it.
I guess I just wasn't thinking.
당연히 그러셨겠지
정신 좀 들게 만들어줄까?
Yeah. Let me give you
something to think about.
잠깐
Hold on! But then I started
thinking and I stopped the kissing.
그러다 정신을 차리고
키스하는 걸 멈췄어
Thank you for taking your tongue out
of my sister's mouth to tell me that.
말이 나오는 걸 보니 혓바닥은
그렇게 오래 집어넣지 않았네
질과 무슨 일이 생기면 너랑은
완전히 끝이라는 생각이 들더라
I realized if anything happened
with me and Jill...
then nothing could ever
happen with us.
뭐?
-What?
-No, I mean...
아니, 내 말은...
우리가 앞으로 어떻게 될지
나로선 장담할 수 없겠지만
I don't know if anything
is ever going to happen with us...
again, ever.
비관적으로 생각하긴 싫어
But I don't want to know
that it never could.
그래서 난 키스를 멈췄고
So I stopped it...
질이 화내는 통에
내 영사기 박살났다
and she got mad
and broke my projector.
Wow.
무슨 말을 해야 하니
I don't even know what to say.
고맙다
Thank you.
별말씀을
You're welcome.
세상에, 자기 지금 울어?
My God, are you crying?
왜 쟤들이 못 합치는 거지?
I just don't see why those two
can't work things out!
좋아, 난 갈게
All right, I'm leaving.
사사건건 참견하는 인간이랑
하루도 같이 있기 싫으니까
I'm not spending one more day with
someone who's out to sabotage me.
언니 말이야
That's you, Rachel.
알고 있었어
Yeah, I got that.
그리고 오빠
And you! I throw myself at you...
온몸으로 달려드는 날 거부해?
오빠 게이 아냐?
and you say no? How gay are you?
몸조심하거라
You take care, Jill.
알았어, 그만 갈게
Okay, I'm leaving. Don't worry
about me, I'll make it on my own.
걱정 마, 난 잘살 거야
Who knows how I'll get by,
or even if I'll survive.
운 좋으면 굶어죽진 않겠지
그만해라, 아빠랑
화해한 거 다 알아
You can stop that now,
I know you made up with Daddy.
-You do? How?
-Oh, just a wild guess...
그건 어떻게?
그냥 찍었어
밖에 리무진 기다린다
and your limo just pulled up.
이렇게 헤어져서 서운해요
-Sorry I didn't get to know you guys better.
-Absolute shame.
우리도 그래
-Okay, see you.
-Bye-bye.
그럼 또 봐요
- 잘 가라
- 안녕
I can't believe Jill's gone.
질이 떠나다니
I can't help it, I opened a gate!
그럼 어떡해
울음보 터졌는걸